Guide to the Walter Isard papers, 1938-1986.
Isard, Walter papers
- Research Proposal: (Including Draft & Supplement), 1974 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- National Science Foundation: Research Proposal--Blackman, 1974 (Box 67, Folder 15)
- NSF Proposal for 1973, 1973 (Box 67, Folder 16)
- N.Y. State Environmental Conservation Commissioner Contract w/ Cornell Univ., 1974 (Box 67, Folder 17)
- Appalachian Reg. Comm. Contract w/N.Y.Dept. of Environ. Conserv., 1974 (Box 67, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 67, Folder 19)
- Environment Reports (Box 67, Folder 20)
- Rotterdam, 1984, 1982-1984 (Box 67, Folder 21)
- 1984 Conferences AAG, Rotterdam, (A), 1983-1984 (Box 67, Folder 22)
- 1984 Conferences AAG, Rotterdam, (B), 1984 (Box 67, Folder 23)
- Chattergji + PSSI + Journal of Peace Science, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 24)
- Journal of Peace Science 1974-1978, 1973-1983 (Box 67, Folder 25)
- Grad Student Correspondence 1977-1983, 1977-1983 (Box 67, Folder 26)
- Misc. Correspondence--late 70's, 80's, 1971-1983 (Box 67, Folder 27)
- Preface, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  Drafts and notes of arms race manuscript
- Chapter 1 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  Drafts of arms race manuscript
- Chapter 2a (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Chapter 2b (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Chapter 3 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Chapter 4 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Chapter 5 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Chapter 6 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Chapter 7 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Chapter 8 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Chapter 9 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Chapter 9 b (Box 68, Folder 12)
- Chapter 10a (Box 68, Folder 13)
- Chapter 10b (Box 68, Folder 14)
- Chapter 11 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Chapter 12 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Chapter 13 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- Chapter 14 (Box 68, Folder 18)
- Chapter 15 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- Chapter 16 (Box 68, Folder 20)
- Glossary (Box 68, Folder 21)
  Glossary notes
- World Energy Models & Studies 1977-78, 1977-1978 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- World Energy Models & Studies Seminar 1978-79, 1978-1979 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- World Energy Seminar Future Topics, 1979-1980 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Seminars--New Seminars, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Air Pollution Grant Applications--July 1, 1971-Aug.31, 1971, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Conference on World Energy Models, May 1977, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Air Pollution--Prior to July 1, 1971, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- E.P.A --Research & Plummer 1973, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Air Pollution Grant--Ruff, Sept. 1, 1971, 1971-1973 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- Highway Research, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- NICHD Proposal--Feb.1, 1972, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- NSSF--Peace, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- NSF--Blackman, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 13)
- NSF Proposal 1974, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Reserve Copies of Grant Proposal--April 1, 1972, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- U17-8327, EPA--House, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Air Pollution Study: 37-913-6102-2, 1970-1972 (Box 69, Folder 17)
- U17-4301, RS-EPA Grant, 1972-1975 (Box 69, Folder 18)
- U91-8307, CQEM--Miller, 1974-1975 (Box 69, Folder 19)
- A-62-8104: Special Studies, Program in Regional Sciences, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 20)
- Palmedo, 1975-1976 (Box 69, Folder 21)
- Brookhaven 414094-S, May 31,1977-Sept. 30, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 22)
- AP00842-02, RS/EPA, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 23)
- U17-8323, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 24)
- Appointments, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 25)
- Barnouzias, T (Box 69, Folder 26)
- Bergen, F., 1972-1973 (Box 69, Folder 27)
- Beyers, William B., 1970-1971 (Box 69, Folder 28)
- Brown, Jay, 1971-1972 (Box 69, Folder 29)
- Cesario, F., 1971-1972 (Box 69, Folder 30)
- Cooke, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 31)
- CUDR Memorandum, 1971-1974 (Box 69, Folder 32)
- CUDR Proposals, 1971-1972 (Box 69, Folder 33)
- Czamanski, 1971-1973 (Box 69, Folder 34)
- Dedekam (Box 69, Folder 35)
- Dehter (Box 69, Folder 36)
- Dokmeci, Vedia (Box 69, Folder 37)
- Economics Dept. (Box 69, Folder 38)
- Falkson (Box 69, Folder 39)
- Gerhardt, Paul, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 40)
- Goldberg, Gary, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 41)
- Goldsmith, Bill, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 42)
- Hewings, 1972-1973 (Box 69, Folder 43)
- Isard, Walter, 1968-1971 (Box 69, Folder 44)
- Jones, Barclay, 1971-1973 (Box 69, Folder 45)
- Kaniss, Phyllis Carole--Regional Science, 1972-1973 (Box 69, Folder 46)
- Kitabatake, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 47)
- Lindsay, Bob, 1971-1972 (Box 69, Folder 48)
- Liossatos, Panagis S., 1970-1971 (Box 69, Folder 49)
- Lim, Kang Won, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 50)
- McClelland, Peter D., 1973 (Box 69, Folder 51)
- Liu, T.C., 1972-1974 (Box 69, Folder 52)
- MacReynolds, W., 1972 (Box 69, Folder 53)
- Mahoney, James, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 54)
- Miller, Ronald--NYDEC, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 55)
- Montgomery, W. David, 1969-1972 (Box 69, Folder 56)
- Outwater, Eric--EPA, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 57)
- Panourgias, Theodore, 1974 (Box 69, Folder 58)
- Theodore Panayiotis Panourgias, 1972-1973 (Box 69, Folder 59)
- Parcels, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 60)
- Parsons, K.C., 1972-1976 (Box 69, Folder 61)
- Personnel, Secretarial, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 62)
- PPRA 715--R.S. 769, Location Theory, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 63)
- Policy Planning + R.A. Dept., 1971 (Box 69, Folder 64)
- Regional Science Department--Division, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 65)
- Regional Science Field, Ph.D. Proposal, 1971-1972 (Box 69, Folder 66)
- Regional Science Brochures--Ph.D. + Postdoctoral, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 67)
- Reiner, Tom, 1972-1973 (Box 69, Folder 68)
- Resources for the Future, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 69)
- Robinson, Frank, 1972-1973 (Box 69, Folder 70)
- Rodwin, L., 1971 (Box 69, Folder 71)
- Romanoff, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 72)
- Rose, Adam, 1972-1974 (Box 69, Folder 73)
- Salama, 1969-1971 (Box 69, Folder 74)
- Saltzman, Dolores, 1974-1976 (Box 69, Folder 75)
- Sharefkin (Box 69, Folder 76)
- Sanders, Wm. (Box 69, Folder 77)
- Semmler, John, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 78)
- Swift, Bert, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 79)
- Urban Studies Field, 1971-1972 (Box 69, Folder 80)
- Winter, Ernst, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 81)
- Watkins, Alfred, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 82)
- Yamada, H, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 83)
- Werczberger, 1969-1971 (Box 69, Folder 84)
- Academic Press, 1969-1970 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Armitage Press, 1977-1978 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Edwards Brothers, 1972-1973 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Elsevier North Holland, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Free Press, 1969-1975 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Heffernan Press, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Lexington Press, 1974-1975 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- McGraw Hill, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- MIT Press, 1971-1978 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Nijhoff, 1977-1978 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Nijhoff, 1977-1979 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- Pion Limited, 1972-1974 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Prentice Hall, 1973-1974 (Box 70, Folder 13)
- Prentice Hall, 1973-1978 (Box 70, Folder 14)
- SAGE, 1972-1977 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- Schenkman Publishing Co., 1968-1970 (Box 70, Folder 16)
- Regional Science & Urban Economics, 1974-1976 (Box 70, Folder 17)
- Regional Science & Urban Economics, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder 18)
- International Regional Science Review, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Northwestern, 1974-1975 (Box 70, Folder 20)
- Post-Keynesian Economics, 1977-1978 (Box 70, Folder 21)
- Conan Institute--Howard, 1974 (Box 70, Folder 22)
- RSA Special Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 70, Folder 23)
- Lapham Award, 1974-1975 (Box 70, Folder 24)
- Ford Foundation--1973, 1973-1975 (Box 70, Folder 25)
- Ford Foundation, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 26)
- Ford Foundation, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 27)
- Ford Foundation 1972, 1972-1976 (Box 70, Folder 28)
- Peace Science Program--WI, 1977-1979 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- RS & PS Seminars--Cornell, 1977 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Isard Class Materials--1982 Fall, Econ 507: Intro to Peace Science, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Upenn--Peace Science: UNH/Dept. (1), 1974-1978 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Upenn--Peace Science Program (2), 1972-1978 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Memos--Peace Science, Upenn (3), 1978 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Upenn--Peace Science (4), 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Upenn--Peace Science, letters to Editors, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Upenn--Peace Science Memos (5), 1977-1978 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Upenn--Peace Science Memos (6), 1971-1976 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Peace Science Unit, 1972-1974 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Reitz + Stellar, 1972-1973 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Department of Peace Research, 1971-1973 (Box 71, Folder 13)
- Peace Science Major, 1972-1975 (Box 71, Folder 14)
- Constitutions--Peace Science Society and Sections (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Peace Science Brochures + Other Material: Upenn, Cornell (Box 71, Folder 16)
- Peace Science Field (Institute) Proposals for Cornell (Box 71, Folder 17)
- 3rd World PSSI Congress, May 30-June3, 1988, 1984-1988 (Box 71, Folder 18)
- WI--Misc. Plans, Ideas (Box 71, Folder 19a)
- Misc. Notes and Ideas (Box 71, Folder 19b)
- Erasmus--Hungary 1978, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 20)
- Karlsruhe--Hungary 1978-1979, 1978-1979 (Box 71, Folder 21)
- Scandinavian Trip, 1972, 1970-1972 (Box 71, Folder 22)
- Disarmament Correspondence --1960, 1959-1961 (Box 71, Folder 23)
- Correspondence: 1974-1978, 1974-1978 (Box 71, Folder 24)
- Isard Class Materials--Econ 606, Fall 1981, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 25)
- Isard Class Materials--Econ 503 (Box 71, Folder 26)
- Isard Class Materials--Econ 605: Advance Social Science Theory (Box 71, Folder 27)
- Misc. Course Materials (Box 71, Folder 28)
- Meeting--Peace Science, Peace Economics, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 29)
- Exams--CRP 832/505, 1974-1985 (Box 71, Folder 30)
- Reading Lists, 1974-1985 (Box 71, Folder 31)
- Appendix A: Data on Air Pollutants by Selected Industries, Processes and Activities, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Recycling--WI & l. Parcels (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Harvard Post-Doc RS Group, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Buffalo Steel Study, 1973 (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Impacts of Environmental Legislation on Economic Development--WI, Alfred Watkins, 1975, 1975 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Impacts of Environmental Legislation (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Cornell University Program In Urban and Regional Studies Annual Report for the Year 1976-1977, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- RS Iron & Steel Report, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Aluminum Report 1977, 1977-1978 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- Philadelphia Input-Output Materials & Procedures, 1964-1967 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- Philadelphia Input-Output, 1965-1968 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Office of Economic Programs, 1961-1962 (Box 72, Folder 12a)
- Philadelphia Input-Output (Box 72, Folder 12b)
- Report on Research for 1953, Harvard Economic Research Project (Box 72, Folder 13)
- ESSA Research Materials (Box 72, Folder 14)
- ESSA Research Materials (Box 72, Folder 15)
- Peace Science 1972--on, 1972-1988 (Box 72, Folder 16)
- WI Appointment at Upenn, 1967-1977 (Box 72, Folder 17)
- RS @ Cornell, 1972-1974 (Box 72, Folder 18)
- RSA Constitutions (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Hierarchy Proposal 1977, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Seminar on Hierarchical Theory--1977, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Horizon, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Horizon--Comparative Cost Analyses (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Horizon--Bibliography & Notes, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Horizon Report, 1975-1977 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Env. Seminar CFIA 1975-76, 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Env. Seminar CFIA 1976-77, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- BNL--Coal Assessment Contract No. 405650-S, 8/77, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- NSF, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- NIH--NSF, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- NSF Research--1977, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Socio-Economic Impact Conference, June 1977, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Socio-Economic Impact Conference, June 1976, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 14)
- CFIA Research, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- CFIA Proposal II, 1976 (Box 73, Folder 16)
- CFIA Proposal I, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 17)
- Complete Set--Environmental Seminar Summaries, 1975-1976 (Box 73, Folder 18)
- World Energy Models & Studies, 1979, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 19)
- World Energy Models Conference, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 20)
- Conference on World Energy Models, 1978, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 21)
- Conference on Future of Northeast States--Jan 25, 1978, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 22)
- Conference on Future of Northeast States--Jan 25, 1978 (2), 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 23)
- Northeast Conference--January, 1979, 1977-1979 (Box 73, Folder 24)
- Conference on Economic Future of Northeast--January 1977, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 25)
- NIH, 1976-1977 (Box 73, Folder 26)
- Environmental Seminar 1974/5, 1974-1975 (Box 73, Folder 27)
- CFIA, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 28)
- Regional Science & Urban Policy--1/78-4/77, 1975-1977 (Box 73, Folder 29a)
- Regional Science & Urban Policy--1977-78, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 29b)
- Regional Science & Urban Policy--1978-1979, 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 29c)
- Regional Science and Urban Policy--1979-1980, 1979-1980 (Box 73, Folder 29d)
- Mailing Lists--Regional Science & Urban Policy, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 30a)
- RSVP Future Topics (Box 73, Folder 30b)
- World Energy Models--Announcements, 1980, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 31a)
- World Energy Models--Mailing Lists, 1977-1978 (Box 73, Folder 31b)
- Peace Science--Hierarchy Seminar, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 32a)
- PcSc. Graduate Seminar (general info), 1979 (Box 73, Folder 32b)
- Peace Science Mailing List(s) (Box 73, Folder 32c)
- Peace Science Seminars Mailings--78-79, (originals etc.), 1978-1979 (Box 73, Folder 32d)
- Peace Science Seminars (originals)--1979-1980, 1979-1980 (Box 73, Folder 32e)
- Peace Science Series (originals) '80-'81, 1980-1981 (Box 73, Folder 32f)
- Peace Science Seminars originals '81-'82, 1981-1982 (Box 73, Folder 32g)
- Peace Science Seminars (general), 1979-1981 (Box 73, Folder 32h)
- Manuscript & Correspondence--Security Product, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Outline of PS Courses, 1974-1978 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Misc. Correspondence & Notes, 1986-88, 1980-1988 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- IIASA Correspondence 1977-78, 1977-1978 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- NY State Contracts, Correspondence 1972-1973, 1972-1973 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Watertown Study Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- U.S.--USSR Exchange Seminar 1978, 1976-1978 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Brookhaven Research 1976-1977, 1976-1977 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Arms Races--Preface & Notes (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Old JPS Corresp., 1982-1984 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Deutsch Correspondence, World University 1976, 1975-1976 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Oct.-Dec. 1979, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Undated Materials (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Sept. 1979, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Jan. - Aug. 1979, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 15)
- July-Dec. 1978, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 16)
- Jan-June 1978, 1978 (Box 74, Folder 17)
- Correspondence 1977, 1977 (Box 74, Folder 18)
- 1974-1976 (Box 74, Folder 19)
- 1957-1973, 1967-1980 (Box 74, Folder 20)
- WAAS ~1980, 1979-1980 (Box 74, Folder 21)
- WAAS ~1980 (2), 1966-1980 (Box 74, Folder 22)
- WAAS, 1965-1968 (Box 74, Folder 23)
- MEST Journal, 1981-1984 (Box 74, Folder 24)
- Misc. Notes (Box 75, Folder 1a)
  Notes, Ch. 13-14 draft
- Preface & Ch. 1 (Box 75, Folder 1b)
  Manuscript--Matching Conflict Situations and Conflict Management Procedures
- Chapter 2 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Chapter 3a (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Chapter 3b (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Chapter 4a (Box 75, Folder 5)
- Chapter 4b (Box 75, Folder 6)
- Chapter 4c (Box 75, Folder 7)
- Chapter 5a (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Chapter 5b (Box 75, Folder 9)
- Chapter 5c (Box 75, Folder 10)
- Chapter 6 (Box 75, Folder 11)
- Chapter 7 (Box 75, Folder 12)
- Chapter 8a (Box 75, Folder 13)
- Chapter 8b (Box 75, Folder 14)
- Chapter 9 (Box 75, Folder 15)
- Chapter 10 (Box 75, Folder 16)
- Chapter 11a (Box 75, Folder 17)
- Chapter 11b (Box 75, Folder 18)
- Chapter 12 (Box 75, Folder 19)
- Chapter 13 (Box 75, Folder 20)
- Chapter 14 (Box 75, Folder 21)
- Chapter 15 (Box 75, Folder 22)
- Misc. Correspondence--A, 1979-1984, 1979-1984 (Box 77, Folder 1a)
- Albegov, Murat, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 1b)
- Anselin, Luc, 1981-1983 (Box 77, Folder 1c)
- Misc. Correspondence--B (1976-1984), 1976-1984 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Batten, David B., 1981-1984 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- Boyce, David E., 1980-1984 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Brotchie, John F., 1979-1984 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Ballinger Publishing Co., 1982-1984 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Misc. Correspondence--C (1979-1984), 1979-1984 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Misc. Correspondence--CH-CU (1978-1983), cont., 1978-1983 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Chatterji, Manas, 1980-1984 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Misc. Correspondence--D (1979-1984), 1979-1984 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Misc. Correspondence--E (1978-1984), 1978-1984 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- Misc. Correspondence--F (1978-1984), 1978-1984 (Box 77, Folder 12)
- Misc. Correspondence--G (1977-1984), 1977-1984 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- Gentile, 1981-1984 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- Misc. Correspondence--H (1978-1984), 1978-1984 (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Misc. Correspondence--I (1978-1984), 1978-1984 (Box 77, Folder 16)
- Misc. Correspondence--J (1979-1984), 1979-1984 (Box 77, Folder 17)
- Karaska, 1978-1985 (Box 77, Folder 18)
- Misc. Correspondence--K, 1978-1984 (Box 77, Folder 19)
- Misc. Correspondence--L (1978-1984), 1978-1984 (Box 77, Folder 20)
- Misc. Correspondence--M (1978-1984), 1978-1984 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- Misc. Correspondence--M (1978-1984), cont., 1978-1984 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Misc. Correspondence--N (1979-1984), 1979-1984 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Misc. Correspondence--O (1979-1984), 1979-1984 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Misc. Correspondence--P (1979-1984), 1979-1984 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Misc. Correspondence--R (1979-1984), 1979-1984 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- Misc. Correspondence--S (1978-1984), 1978-1984 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Misc. Correspondence--S (1978-1984) cont., 1978-1984 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Misc. Correspondence--T (1978-1984), 1978-1984 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Misc. Correspondence--U (1979-1984), 1979-1984 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Misc. Correspondence--V (1980-1984), 1980-1984 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Misc. Correspondence--W (1977-1984), 1977-1984 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Misc. Correspondence--X, Y,Z (1979-1984), 1979-1984 (Box 78, Folder 13)
- Misc. Correspondence--(-1983), 1973-1983 (Box 78, Folder 14)
- Misc. Correspondence--1984, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Misc. Correspondence--1984 cont., 1984 (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Misc. Correspondence--1985, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Misc. Correspondence--1985 cont., 1985 (Box 78, Folder 18)
- Misc. Correspondence--1986, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 19)
- Misc. Correspondence (1987-1992), 1987-1992 (Box 78, Folder 20)
- Undated (Box 78, Folder 21)
- NSF Proposal 1981-1982 Last One, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder Item 1)
- Integration of Multiregional Models NSF Proposal, 1982-1983 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- Conference Research Draft Papers, 1982 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- Research Reports 1980, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Upenn Proposal Forms, 1983, 1983 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- Modeling and Regional Statistical Analysis Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- National-Regional Impact Evaluation System (Box 79, Folder Item 7)
- Multi-Regional Model Study (Box 79, Folder 8)
- Research Studies for Policy Analysis & Forecasting, 1981 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- Research Studies on Regional Modeling, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- Integrated Multi-Regional Model NSF Proposal, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- Research studies for NSF proposal, 1980 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- NSF Proposal Written Draft and Additions (Box 79, Folder 13)
- NSF Grants Re: Models (Multiregional)+ Correspondence ~1980, 1979-1980 (Box 79, Folder 14)
- NSF Research Materials + Correspondence, 1980-1984 (Box 79, Folder 15)
- Studies Re: Regional Planning & Economic Analysis, 1980-1981, 1980-1981 (Box 79, Folder 16)
- Integration of Multi-regional Models for Policy Analysis (Box 79, Folder 17)
- Multi-Region Proposal Original (Box 79, Folder 18)
- Integration of Multi-regional Models Study & Materials (Box 79, Folder 19)
- NSF Study--Research Materials (Box 79, Folder 20)
- Cornell Student Misc., 1982 (Box 79, Folder 21)
- NSF Proposal & Response, 1983 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Curriculum Vitae (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Notes, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 3)
- NSF Proposal, 1984 (Box 80, Folder 4)
- NSF Letters Re: Proposal 1983-84, 1983-1984 (Box 80, Folder 5)
- NSF Letters Re: Proposal 1984-85, 1984-1985 (Box 80, Folder 6)
- NSF Proposal (Box 80, Folder 7)
- Budgets (Box 80, Folder 8)
- Multiregional Models NSF Proposal--Vol. 3 (Box 80, Folder 9)
- Multiregional Models NSF Proposal--Vol. 2 (Box 80, Folder 10)
- Multiregional Models NSF Proposal--Vol. 2 (Box 80, Folder 11)
- Vol. 1a (Box 80, Folder 12)
- Volume 1b (Box 80, Folder 13)
- Factin (Box 80, Folder 14)
  Section on Factor Demand and Investment Module (FACTIN)
- Appendices (Box 80, Folder 15)
  Appendices A, G
- Trans (Box 80, Folder 16)
  Transportation Module subcontract to Univ. of Illinois, appendix C
- CICIOP (Box 80, Folder 17)
  Comparative cost, industrial complex, input-output, programming model section; appendix B
- Diagrams (Box 80, Folder 18)
- REGLEC (Box 80, Folder 19)
  Multiregional econometric module section, Appendix D, notes
- DEMO (Box 80, Folder 20)
  Demo section--the Microanalytic Population Module
- Notations (Box 80, Folder 21)
- Correspondence --Integrated Multi. Model (Box 80, Folder 22)
  NSF response to proposal, Isard's reaction to reviews
- Southern Report Materials, 1981-1982 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  Kansas City Southern Railway (KCSR)
- Phase 1 Technical Report: Economic Base Analysis for the Houston-Galveston Region, 1979-1980 (Box 81, Folder Item 2)
- Verified Statement of Walter Isard--Feb., Sept. 1981, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 3)
- Verified Statement of WI, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 4)
- Verified Statement of Walter Isard, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 5)
- Notes for Analysis of Kansas City Southern Project, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Interstate Commerce Commission KCSR Statements of Witnesses in Rebuttal, 1981 (Box 81, Folder Item 7)
- Interstate Commerce Commission KCSR Brief Vol.2 of 2, 1982 (Box 81, Folder Item 8)
- Verified Statements of Witnesses, Part 1, 1981 (Box 81, Folder Item 9)
- Verified Statement of WI, Work papers (Box 81, Folder 10)
- Industrial Site Map: Lower Mississippi River (Box 81, Folder 11)
- Aluminum Industry, 1976-1977 (Box 82, Folder 1)
- Petrochemical Technology Including Changing Feedstock, 1976-1977 (Box 82, Folder 2)
- Iron & Steel 1970s (Box 82, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Articles--Aluminum (Box 82, Folder 4)
- Iron & Steel 2 (Box 82, Folder 5)
- Walter Isard & Larry Parcels, Dec. 1977, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Articles--Petrochemicals (Junk) (Box 82, Folder 7)
- Energy--Petrol + Nat. Gas (Junk) (Box 82, Folder 8)
- Petrochemical Demand Projections (Box 82, Folder 9)
- Demand for Petrochemical Intermed. (Box 82, Folder 10)
- Shell Oil Correspondence--Reports, 1973-1976 (Box 82, Folder 11)
- W. Miernyk--Energy Articles, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 12)
- KCS, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 13)
- KCS, 1980-1981 (Box 82, Folder 14)
- KCS, 1981 (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Global Studies: Early 80's, 1981-1983 (Box 82, Folder 16)
- World Models (Box 82, Folder Item 17)
- Global Studies: Early 80's, 1979-1982 (Box 82, Folder 18)
- Papers, Global Studies, 1980 (Box 82, Folder 19)
- Global Studies notes, papers, 1981-1984 (Box 82, Folder 20)
- RSA Nov. 1983 paper, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 21)
- AAG Denver 1983, 1983 (Box 82, Folder 22a)
- AAG--Denver 1983 Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 82, Folder 22b)
- Political Geog. Sessions AAG 1984, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 1)
- RSA Finances 1980-86, 1, 1979-1986 (Box 83, Folder 2)
- RSA Finances 1980-86, 2, 1985-1986 (Box 83, Folder 3)
- RSA Finances 1980-86, 3, 1985-1986 (Box 83, Folder 4)
- RSA Finances 1980-86, 4, 1984-1986 (Box 83, Folder 5)
- RSA Finances 1980-86, 5, 1985-1986 (Box 83, Folder 6)
- Larry Smarr-Computer Work 1984-1985, 1984-1985 (Box 83, Folder 7)
- 2nd WU--Peace Science Congress, Rotterdam--1, 1982-1984 (Box 83, Folder 8)
- 2nd WU--Peace Science Congress, Rotterdam--2, 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 9)
- 2nd WU--PSSI Conf., Rotterdam--3, 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 10)
- 2nd WU--PSSI World Conf., Rotterdam--4, 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- 2nd WU--PSSI World Conf., Rotterdam--5, 1983-1984 (Box 83, Folder 12)
- 2nd WU--PSSI World Conf., Rotterdam--6, 1982-1984 (Box 83, Folder 13)
- Ecologic Economic Book: Section 1.1 Moorings (Box 83, Folder 14a)